<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- generator="Joomla! 1.5 - Open Source Content Management" -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="/components/com_jcomments/tpl/default/style.css?v=10" type="text/css"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>April 2010</title>
		<description>Rollins Archive</description>
		<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010.html</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 13:38:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>Joomla! 1.5 - Open Source Content Management</generator>
		<language>en-gb</language>
		<item>
			<title>#14: April 03, 2010</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/105-14-april-03-2010.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/105-14-april-03-2010.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2010/April/apr03.zip">#14: April 03, 2010</a></p>

<div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-right: 0px; margin-bottom: 0.75em; margin-left: 0px; line-height: 1.6em;">01. The Ramones - I Just Wanna Have Something To Do<br />02. The Cramps - Garbage Man<br />03. Flin Flon - Upper Ferry<br />04. Generation X - Untouchables<br />05. Tel Aviv - I Have Met A Writer<br />06. Rites Of Spring - All Through A Life<br />07. The Adverts - Television's Over<br />08. UK Subs - Perfect Girl<br />09. DEVO - Be Stiff (Stiff version)<br />10. The Lurkers - Cyanide<br />11. The Lurkers - Cyanide (Pub Version)<br />12. The Damned - Smash It Up Parts 1-4<br />13. The Ruts - It Was Cold<br />14. The Teen Idles - Trans AM<br />15. Alan Vega Trio - Freedom<br />16. The Buzzcocks - Breakdown<br />17. The Enzymes - Speedwash<br />18. The Angelic Upstarts - Teenage Warning<br />19. The Skunks - Good From The Bad <br />20. Brian Eno - Dead Finks Don't Talk<br />21. Empire - Hot Seat<br />22. Pure Hell - No Rules<br />23. The Models - Man Of The Year<br />24. Clear - Whirl<br />25. The Untouchables - I Hate You<br />26. Egg Hunt - Me And You</div>

<div></div>
<div style="margin-top: 0px; margin-right: 0px; margin-bottom: 0.75em; margin-left: 0px; line-height: 1.6em;"></div>
<div></div>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>April 2010</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 22:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#15: April 10, 2010</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/222-15-april-10-2010.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/222-15-april-10-2010.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2010/April/apr10.zip">#15: April 10, 2010</a></p>

<p>01. Aksak Maboul - A Modern Lesson<br /> 02. Helios Creed - Throw Away The Rind<br /> 03. Tangerine Dream - Ashes To Ashes<br /> 04. Team Doyobi - Per Aspera Ad Astra<br /> 05. Don Sornrabeab - Mao (Drunk)<br /> 06. Television - See No Evil<br /> 07. Terakaft - Legh Assistane Dagh Aïtma<br /> 08. Hawnay Troof - Give Me Something<br /> 09. Slim Harpo - Don't Start Crying Now (single version)<br /> 10. Frank Wright - Grooving<br /> 11. Black Tambourine - Black Car<br /> 12. Stains Get - Revenge<br /> 13. Gene Vincent - Cat Man<br /> 14. Hans Joachim Roedelius - Goldregen<br /> 15. Jaguar Love - Antoine And Birdskull<br /> 16. Kraftwerk - Antenne <br /> 07. Bobadin - Di Kanar Manut/ The Hut <br /> 18. Scatman Crothers - The Best Things In Life Are Free<br /> 19. Ice-Cubists - The Cravats<br /> 20. De La Soul - Jenifa Taught Me<br /> 21. The Fontaine Toups - TFT<br /> 22. Birthday Party - Cat Man<br /> 23. Adverts - Safety In Numbers<br /> 24. Arditti String Quartet - String Quartet No. 1 "Métamorphoses      Nocturnes"<br /> 25. Flower Travellin' Band - Heaven And Hell<br /> 26. King Tubby And Friends - Step It Up In Dub<br /> 27. The Clash - Capital Radio One<br /> 28. The Horrors - Who Says<br /> 29. Sun Ra - This Song Is Dedicated To Nature's God</p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>April 2010</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#16: April 17, 2010</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/223-16-april-17-2010.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/223-16-april-17-2010.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://rollins-archive.com/2010/April/apr17.zip">#16: April 17, 2010<br /></a></p>

<p>*Fanatics - I made a boo-boo with the file name. It reads #17 April 17, 2010, when it should read #16 April 17, 2010. Just ignore me for now. I plan on re-recording the show and putting a new file up - something about this one sounds a little compressed to me so I want to fix that. I'm on tour right now so bear with me until I get the chance to fix all this. Oh, and welcome to the new site.*</p>
<p>*UPDATE May 02, 2010 - fixed the file and re-recorded the show so it  should sound better now. 'Should' being the operative word here. I'll  check it out later.</p>
<p>01. Jimi Hendrix - Changes<br /> 02. Ike Yard - We Are One<br /> 03. Rowland Howard - Pop Crimes<br /> 04. Monty Python - I Bet They Won't Play This Song On The  Radio<br /> 05. The Mob - Shuffling Souls<br /> 06. Creedence Clearwater Revival - Fortunate Son<br /> 07. Japandroids - Wet Hair<br /> 08. The Buzzcocks - Fast Cars <br /> 09. Cab Calloway - The Scat Song<br /> 10. The Birthday Party - Bully Bones<br /> 11. Riot Clone - Neu-Vestation<br /> 12. Frank Wright - The Lady<br /> 13. Air Miami - Warm Miami May<br /> 14. Glaxo Babies - Who Killed Bruce Lee<br /> 15. Concrete - Farming Today<br /> 16. Istîkhbar - Mohamed Khaznadji<br /> 17. Robert Pete Williams - Your Troubles Gonna Be Like Mine<br /> 18. The Bevis Frond - Splendid Isolation<br /> 19. Captain Beefheart - The Past Sure Is Tense<br /> 20. Pan Ron - Ooh...He's Mute<br /> 21. Camberwell Now - Element Unknown<br /> 22. Krokodil - Blue Flashing Circle<br /> 23. Amampondo - Tere Tere<br /> 24. Windy & Carl - Universal Energy<br /> 25. Snail - Cleanliness<br /> 26. Two Guys - Crazy Little Notion<br /> 27. The Fall - Kimble<br /> 28. Dizu Plaatjes - Outalo Ntsintsi<br /> 29. The Aquarium - White House<br /> 30. Television - Prove It</p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>April 2010</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#17: April 24, 2010</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/394-17-april-24-2010.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2010/april-2010/394-17-april-24-2010.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p>FANATICS!! Welcome back. Do excuse the long delay in getting this new site up and running. I'm on tour in Germany/Switzerland for the past few weeks so I've been jumping online whenever I could to put in all the info from the previous site - on kerbs outside cafes, on the bus when a signal permitted, and in hotels if they didn't ask for a kidney. With 6 years of weekly posts, and just as many comments, you can imagine how long that took for each individual show to be copied. But we're Fanatics!!!! And we're worth it!!!</p>

<p>If anything isn't working like it should let me know. I'm pretty sure I put everything up here correctly but if ever there was room for human error it was about 457 posts ago. So, until next week - STAY FANATIC!!!</p>
<p>*Many many thanks to RikRokSMC for all things binary. Without him this would all just say 'R-TYPE: Loading Error'*</p>
<p><span><span><a href="http://rollins-archive.com/2010/April/apr24.zip">#17: April 24,  2010</a> </span></span> <span><span><br /></span></span><br /> 01. The Fall - Lie Dream Of A Casino Soul<br /> 02. Mohamed Khaznadji - Mode Ghrib<br /> 03. Kaleidoscope - A Dream For Julie<br /> 04. Lake Of Dracula - Cherries And Socks<br /> 05. Tangerine Dream - Sunrise In The Third System<br /> 06. Art Tatum - Stompin' At The Savoy<br /> 07. Suicide - Power Au Go-Go<br /> 08. Various Artists - Congolaise Benin Ye<br /> 09. Cedell Davis - She's Got The Devil In Her<br /> 10. Dead Boys - Sonic Reducer<br /> 11. The Bags - We Will Bury You<br /> 12. Bernard Herrmann - Klaatu            <br /> 13. Dillinger - Ragnampiza<br /> 14. Eddy Current Suppression Ring - It's All Square<br /> 15. Al Eide - Up Not Down<br /> 16. Einstürzende Neubauten - Ehrlicher Stein<br /> 17. Unrest - Angel I'll Walk You Home<br /> 18. Unrest - Cath Carroll<br /> 19. Unrest - So Sick <br /> 20. Unrest - Light Command<br /> 21. Unrest - Food & Drink Synthesizer<br /> 22. Unrest - Soon It Is Going To Rain<br /> 23. Unrest - Make Out Club<br /> 24. Unrest - Breather X.O.X.O.<br /> 25. Unrest - West Coast Love Affair<br /> 26. Unrest - Six Layer Cake<br /> 27. Unrest - Stylized Ampersand</p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>April 2010</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 09:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>

</rss>
