<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- generator="Joomla! 1.5 - Open Source Content Management" -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="/components/com_jcomments/tpl/default/style.css?v=10" type="text/css"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>November 2009</title>
		<description>Rollins Archive</description>
		<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009.html</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 14:40:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>Joomla! 1.5 - Open Source Content Management</generator>
		<language>en-gb</language>
		<item>
			<title>#45: November 07, 2009</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/162-45-november-07-2009.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/162-45-november-07-2009.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<span><span><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2009/November/nov07.zip">November  07, 2009</a></span></span>

<div><span><span></span></span><br />
<div><span><span>Fanatics,  there's a problem with the end of the broadcast - the audio is  corrupted on some level. I've checked this with two different recordings  (thanks D.) and the KCRW listen again broadcast and sadly it's on the  there too.</span></span></div>
<div><span><span></span></span><br />

<div>And  for the October 31 broadcast, the ending is fixed and will be up  shortly.</div>
<div><span><span><br />01. The Jimi Hendrix  Experience – Exp<br />02. Hawkwind - Veterans Of A Thousand Psychic Wars<br />03.  The Firesign Theatre - The Giant Toad<br />04. Skullbot – Psychic<br />05.  Tsuxma - Sagari-Ha<br />06. Roky Erickson And The Aliens - Two Headed Dog<br />07.  Julee Cruise - Falling<br />08. The Rolling Stones – Respectable<br />09.  Dr. Alimantado - Mash It Up<br />10. Philip Lynott - Dear Miss Lonely  Hearts<br />11. Kieran Hebden & Steve Reid – Greensleeves<br />12. Black  Randy & The Metro Squad - I Slept In An Arcade<br />13. Hank Mizell -  Jungle Rock<br />14. Joseph K - Pictures (Of Cindy)<br />15. Scrapper  Blackwell - Hard Time Blues<br />16. Thelonious Monk Quartet w/ John  Coltrane - Blue Monk<br />17. Frank Zappa - Who Are The Brain Police?<br />18.  Lydia Kavina - Suite From "Bählamms Fest": VII<br />19. The Matt Ritvo  Group - The Path<br />20. Electric Wizard - We Hate You<br />21. The Fall -  Jungle Rock<br />22. Lake Of Dracula – Violators<br />23. The Last Poets -  Related To What<br />24. El Guapo - Hollywood Crew<br />25. Van Halen -  Ain't Talkin' 'Bout Love<br />26. The Velvet Underground - Black Angel's  Death Song (mono)</span></span></div>

</div>
</div>
<p><em>posted by Mr.Hughes </em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>November 2009</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#46: November 14, 2009 - Guest Host Shepard Fairey </title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/164-46-november-14-2009-guest-host-shepard-fairey-.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/164-46-november-14-2009-guest-host-shepard-fairey-.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2009/November/nov14.zip">November  14, 2009</a></div>

<p>01. John Coltrane - Greensleeves  (thanks Luke)<br />02. Lou Reed - Perfect Day (live)<br />03. Iggy Pop -  China Girl<br />04. David Bowie - Prettiest Star<br />05. T-Rex - 20th  Century Boy<br />06. Girlschool & Motorhead - Please Don't Touch<br />07.  Motorhead - Louie Louie<br />08. Beastie Boys - Pass The Mic<br />09. Bad  Brains - The Big Takeover<br />10. Minor Threat - Stepping Stone<br />11.  The Monkees - Mary Mary<br />12. Run DMC - It's Tricky<br />13. The Knack -  My Sharona<br />14. The Sweet - Ballroom Blitz<br />15. Blondie - One Way Or  Another<br />16. Richard Hell & The Voidoids - Blank Generation<br />17.  Ramones - Rock And Roll Radio<br />18. The Specials - Concrete Jungle<br />19.  Elvis Costello & The Attractions - Pump It Up<br />20. The Go-Go's -  Our Lips Are Sealed<br />21. X - Nausea<br />22. The Doors - Peace Frog<br />23.  Iggy And The Stooges - I Wanna Be Your Dog<br />24. The MC5 - I Can Only  Give You Everything<br />25. Velvet Underground - Sweet Jane<br />26. Beck -  Devil's Haircut<br />27. Public Enemy - Public Enemy No.1<br />28. Suicidal  Tendencies - Institutionalized</p>

<p><em>posted by Mr.Hughes</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>November 2009</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#47: November 21, 2009</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/163-47-november-21-2009.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/163-47-november-21-2009.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<span><span><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2009/November/nov21.zip">November  21, 2009</a></span></span>

<div><span><span><br />01. Empire  – Your Electric Guitar<br />02. Iggy Pop – Bang Bang<br />03. Amanaz – Easy  Street<br />04. Frank Zappa - Apostrophe<br />05. Lieutenant Caramel – Le  Harmonie Usee<br />06. The Horrors – Scarlet Fields<br />07. Aneka  Palaran–Bawa Dandangula Ban Yumasan Kalagengaken<br />08. Neville Marcano –  War<br />09. Engineer X - Mash<br />10. Meat Puppets – Swimming Ground<br />11.  The Minutemen – Cut<br />12. Husker Du – Makes No Sense At All<br />13. The  Buzzcocks – Airwaves Dream<br />14. Joy Division - Interzone<br />15. Wire -  Lowdown<br />16. Revolutionary Corps. Of Teenage Jesus – Puzz Puzz<br />17.  Little Richard – Good Golly Ms. Molly<br />18. Air Miami – Afternoon  Train<br />19. Soccer Team – A Cavity Called Home<br />20. Georgie James -  More Lights<br />21. Jaguar Love – Jaguar Pirates<br />22. Hudan - Bubaran  (Golden Rain)<br />23. Vladimir Vysotsky – Sail<br />24. Isaac Hayes – Walk  From Regio’s<br />25. Evening Prayer – Yogyakarta Mosque (evening)<br />26.  No Name – Commitment</span></span></div>

<p><em>posted by Mr.Hughes</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>November 2009</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#48: November 28, 2009</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/165-48-november-28-2009.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2009/november-2009/165-48-november-28-2009.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<div>

<div><span><span><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2009/November/nov28.zip">November  28, 2009</a></span></span>
<div><span><span><br /> </span></span>
<div><span><span>01.  Wolfman Jack / Marathons - Peanut Butter<br />02. The Ramones - The  Return of Jackie And Judy<br />03. Chrome - TV As Eyes<br />04. Tèshomè  Meteku - Gara Ser Nèw Bétesh<br />05. The Fall - Married Two Kids<br />06.  Skip James - Cherry Ball Blues<br />07. Ivo Papasov - Byala Stala<br />08.  Witch - Soul Of Fire<br />09. Excepter - Whirl Wind<br />10. The Shangri-Las  - Sophisticated Boom Boom<br />11. Charles De Goal – Synchro<br />12.  Scientist - Blood On His Lips<br />13. Unrest – Christina<br />14. The  Urinals - Ack Ack Ack Ack<br />15. Minutemen - Ack Ack Ack Ack<br />16. The  Weirdos - Fort U.S.A.<br />17. Blonde Redhead - For The Damaged<br />18.  Bootsy Collins - Rubber Duckie<br />19. Jimi Hendrix - 1983...(A Merman I  Should Turn To Be)<br />20. Empire - All These Things<br />21. Christaliers -  Homeroom Rock<br />22. Richard Hell & The Voidoids - Blank Generation<br />23.  Shelley / Devoto - Stupid Kunst<br />24. Jürgen Hocker - Études pour  piano: IX. Vertige<br />25. EL Guapo – Hawks<br />26. Duke Ellington - Suite  Thursday: Schwiphti<br />27. The Vibrators - Judy Says . . .<br />28. Joe  Meek - Love Dance Of The Saroos<br />29. Raymond Scott - And The Dish Ran  Away With The Spoon<br />30. Bob Dylan – All Along The Watchtower<br />31.  Captain Beefheart - The Dust Blows Forward 'n The Dust Blows Back</span></span></div>

</div>
</div>
</div>
<p><em>posted by Mr.Hughes</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>November 2009</category>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

