<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- generator="Joomla! 1.5 - Open Source Content Management" -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="/components/com_jcomments/tpl/default/style.css?v=10" type="text/css"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>January 2007</title>
		<description>Rollins Archive</description>
		<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007.html</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 14:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>Joomla! 1.5 - Open Source Content Management</generator>
		<language>en-gb</language>
		<item>
			<title>#1: January 02, 2007</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/224-1-january-02-2007.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/224-1-january-02-2007.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p>I hope you all enjoyed the holidays. I  believe this is the last of the pre-taped shows, so maybe next week will  be live again. Please visit the <a href="http://harmonyinmyhead.com/">official  site</a> for more track information. In case you haven't noticed yet  (or read the previous post), I've cleaned up the <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/fantasies/">Fanatic! Fantasies</a> section. Anything you find there now is available for download directly.  I have a few older posts pending and I will add those as soon as I get  the files.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan02part1.zip">Part  One</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan02part2.zip">Part  Two</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan02part3.zip">Part  Three</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan02part4.zip">Part  Four</a><br /><br />01. Black Flag - Fix Me<br />02. Viletones –  Rebel<br />03. Ramones - Rockaway Beach<br />04. Iggy And The Stooges -  Tight Pants<br />05. The Dregs - I'm Insane<br />06. Lightnin' Hopkins -  Happy New Year<br />07. Raymond Scott - New Year's Eve In A Haunted House<br />08.  Woody Guthrie - Los Angeles New Year's Flood<br />09. Isaac Hayes - The  Mistletoe And Me<br />10. Tenor Saw - Ring The Alarm (Live)<br />11. The  Clash – Cheat<br />12. Buzzcocks – ESP<br />13. Generation X - Day By Day<br />14.  Sleep – Dragonaut<br />15. Suicide - Rocket USA<br />16. The Ruts -  Something That I Said<br />17. The Fall - Cab It Up!<br />18. Julee Cruise -  The Nightingale<br />19. The Damned - Born To Kill<br />20. Slim Gaillard  & Slam Stewart - Ferdinand The Bull<br />21. Funkadelic - Super Stupid<br />22.  Wire - Two People In A Room<br />23. The Screamer – Infant Son<br />24.  Devo – Shout (E-Z Listening version)</p>

<p><em>posted by Rollins-Archive</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>January 2007</category>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#2: January 9, 2007 - Thanks Stuart! </title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/226-2-january-9-2007-thanks-stuart-.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/226-2-january-9-2007-thanks-stuart-.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p>Thank you to Stuart for sending the first  half of the show. I was having connection problems and it took about  half the show to get it going again. This week was not a live show, but  still a good one. Please visit the <a href="http://harmonyinmyhead.com/">official  site</a> for the track info. Be sure to check out the <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/fantasies/">Fanatic!Fantasies</a> section. There's a great set there from Dick that includes a rare Pink  Floyd track. He's also included track notes with his set, so don't miss  out. More of the older sets have been added as well.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan9part1.zip">Part  One</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan9part2.zip">Part  Two</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan9part3.zip">Part  Three</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan9part4.zip">Part  Four</a><br /><br /> 01. X - Johnny Hit And Run Paulene<br />02.  Birthday Party - Blast Off<br />03. The Fall - So Called Dangerous<br />04.  Public Image Ltd. - Public Image<br />05. Public Enemy - Public Enemy #1  (Demo)<br />06. The Ruts – Backbiter<br />07. Squatweiler - Hot For Teacher<br />08.  Parliament - Mr. Wiggles<br />09. The Inspirations - You Know What I Mean<br />10.  Sleater-Kinney - Night Light<br />11. The Firesign Theatre - The  Chinchilla Show<br />12. Flipper - Ha Ha Ha<br />13. Bobby Byrd - Hot Pants -  I'm Coming<br />14. The Stains - Sick And Crazy<br />15. The Clash - Remote  Control<br />16. Casual Dots - Mama's Gonna Make Us A Cake<br />17. Harriet  Tubman - Asiatic Research<br />18. Juliana Hatfield - My Pet Lion<br />19.  Jimi Hendrix – Remember<br />20. Dinosaur Jr. - I Don't Think So<br />21.  The Castaways - Liar, Liar<br />22. Muluqèn Mèllèsè - Wètètié Maré<br />23.  The Wall – Ghetto<br />24. Blondie - X Offender<br />25. Wire – Surgeon’s  Girl<br />26. Wolf Eyes – Damzel</p>

<p><em>posted by Rollins-Archive</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>January 2007</category>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#3: January 16, 2007</title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/227-3-january-16-2007.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/227-3-january-16-2007.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p>According to the <a href="http://harmonyinmyhead.com/">official site</a>, this is the last of  the pre-taped shows. Next week should be a brand new live broadcast.  For those of you who noticed a new link on this site over the weekend  only to find that it went nowhere, sorry! It's fixed now. It's the link  labeled "<a href="http://jpwilley.blogspot.com/">mindriot & black  coffee</a>" and it takes you to the blogger page of our fellow fanatic  Patrick's two radio shows out of Minturn, Colorado.</p>

<p>And now for a very special shout out to an Aussie tyke  who could very well be the youngest fanatic-in-training out there. <span style="font-family: lucida grande;"><em><strong>Happy 1st Birthday,  Sam!</strong></em></span> Sam's proud papa is the creator of the <a href="http://www.justdamnedpunk.blogspot.com/">justdamnedpunk</a> podcast. Check it out, rock out to some awesome punk, and wish little  Sam a happy birthday!<br /><br /><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan16part1.zip">Part  One</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan16part2.zip">Part  Two</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan16part3.zip">Part  Three</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan16part4.zip">Part  Four</a><br /><br />01. Gunung Jati Ensemble Of Tegas -  Gambang Kuta<br />02. Laurie Anderson - Sharkey's Night<br />03. Dr.  Alimantado - Mash It Up<br />04. David Bowie - Look Back In Anger<br />05.  Betty Davis - Don't Call Her No Tramp<br />06. Television – Venus<br />07.  The Fall - Green Eyed Loco Man<br />08. James Brown - There It Is (parts  1&2)<br />09. Buzzcocks - Harmony in My Head<br />10. Nick Cave &  The Bad Seeds - Red Right Hand<br />11. Wire – I Am The Fly<br />12. PJ  Harvey - Meet Ze Monsta<br />13. Hanoi Rocks - Back To Mystery City<br />14.  Miles Davis - Directions II<br />15. Newtown Neurotics – Hypocrite<br />16.  X - Blue Spark<br />17. Cramps - I'm Cramped (original mix)<br />18.  Masanka Sankayi+Kasai All-stars - Wa Muluendu<br />19. The Clash – 1977<br />20.  Oil Tasters - That's When The Brick Goes Through The Window<br />21. The  Blood Brothers - Rat Rider<br />22. Arak Music - Ni Maan<br />23. Can -  Tango Whiskyman</p>

<p><em>posted by Rollins-Archive</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>January 2007</category>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#4: January 23, 2007 - UPDATED 01/31/07 </title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/228-4-january-23-2007-updated-013107-.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/228-4-january-23-2007-updated-013107-.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p>[UPDATE: Stuart sent in a terrestrial  recording of the first few minutes so we can hear what the web stream  was trying to cover with a commercial. I spliced it into the recording I  had for part one. The link below is for the new file, if you want to  redownload it. There was some static, especially in the first few  seconds, and I monkeyed around with the sound a bit so it sounds a  little weird. You can really tell where the splices are but it's talking  and not music, so it's not too bad. Thanks again, Stuart!]<br /><br />Thanks  to everyone at <a href="http://www.21361.com/">21361</a> for being nice  to me today and not mistaking me for a kook. And just in case any of  you know the nut out there that thinks Henry's tattoos are talking to  them, please let them know that I hope the tattoos are telling them to  lay off the crack for a while. Moving on.... I put a link up for the <a href="http://www.wm3.org/">West Memphis Three</a> website. Many of you  already know about it, but for those of you who don't please check it  out. This week's show is in 3 parts because the first hour was  commercial-free and I didn't want to chop it up.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan23part1b.zip">Part  One (updated)</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan23part2.zip">Part  Two</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan23part3.zip">Part  Three</a><br /><br />01. The Stains - Gang Related Death<br />02.  Ahmad Muhammad Ahmad - Torab-Taqsim Nay<br />03. James "Iron Head" Baker -  Black Betty<br />04. Nick Cave & The Bad Seeds - Black Betty<br />05.  Kim Salmon & the Surrealists – Radiation<br />06. Pere Ubu - Chinese  Radiation<br />07. Public Image Ltd. - Low Life<br />08. Nikki Sudden And  Rowland S. Howard - Sob Story<br />09. Andrej & Tschetschek -  Tschasky-Chem Yry<br />10. Gene Defcon – Toss That Fish Back<br />11.  Various Artists - Farhang-E A'vâm<br />12. The Voice - The Train To  Disaster<br />13. Ari-Up - Exterminator<br />14. Desmond Dekker & The  Aces – Warlock<br />15. The Saints - This Perfect Day (single version)<br />16.  The Fall - This Perfect Day<br />17. Epsilons - Fever To Kill<br />18.  Brian Eno - Here He Comes<br />19. The Aquarium - Can't Afford To Live  Here<br />20. Black Dice – Twins<br />21. Tinariwen - Chet Boghassa<br />22.  Gil Evans - Where Flamingos Fly<br />23. Yellow Swans - The Bombs That  Keep Dropping Make It Hard To Sleep<br />24. The Spaniels – Goodnight,  Sweetheart, Goodnight</p>

<p><em>posted by Rollins-Archive</em></p>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>January 2007</category>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>#5: January 30, 2007 - Stuart Saves the Day: The Sequel </title>
			<link>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/229-5-january-30-2007-stuart-saves-the-day-the-sequel-.html</link>
			<guid>http://rollins-archive.com/2007/january-2007/229-5-january-30-2007-stuart-saves-the-day-the-sequel-.html</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[A big thank you to Stuart for sending in his  terrestrial radio recording for the second half of the show (part  three)!<br /><br /><a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan30part1.zip">Part  One</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan30part2.zip">Part  Two</a> * <a href="http://www.rollins-archive.com/2007/January/jan30part3.zip">Part  Three</a><br /><br />01. The Medallions / Wolfman Jack -  Peanut Butter<br />02. Chrome - TV As Eyes<br />03. Tèshomè Meteku - Gara  Ser Nèw Bétesh<br />04. The Fall - Married Two Kids<br />05. Skip James –  Cherry Ball Blues<br />06. Ivo Papasov & His Orchestra - Byala Stala<br />07.  Witch - Soul Of Fire<br />08. Excepter - Whirl Wind<br />09. The  Shangri-Las - Sophisticated Boom Boom<br />10. Charles De Goal – Synchro<br />11.  Scientist - Blood On His Lips<br />12. Unrest – Christina<br />13. The  Urinals - Ack Ack Ack Ack<br />14. The Minutemen - Ack Ack Ack Ack<br />15.  The Weirdos – Fort USA<br />16. Blonde Redhead - For The Damaged<br />17.  Bootsy Collins - Rubber Duckie<br />18. Jimi Hendrix - 1983... (A Merman I  Should Turn To Be)<br />19. Christaliers - Homeroom Rock<br />20. György  Ligeti - Études Pour Piano Part IX<br />21. El Guapo – Hawks<br />22. Duke  Ellington - Suite Thursday: Schwiphti<br />23. John Cale – Chickenshit<br />24.  Buzzkunst - Stupid Kunst<br />25. Empire - All These Things<br />26. Joe  Meek - Love Dance Of The Saroos<br /><br /><em>posted by Rollins-Archive</em>]]></description>
			<author>mr.hughes@hotmail.com (Gareth Hughes)</author>
			<category>January 2007</category>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>

</rss>
